welcome to the idea cafe this is the
video where I explain the ins and outs
of what the idea cafe yes so what it is
is a youtube channel clearly to
participate in a conversation around a
meaningful question who gets to
participate in those videos is everyone
and anyone any individual who wants to
discuss that week's question live on
camera no expertise is needed you do not
need to already be an influencer all you
have to do is bring you that is what we
are doing here is showing the power of a
conversation show up as you are with
your experience your ideas your feelings
when we are starting with one timeslot a
week Wednesdays 11:00 a.m. Pacific
Standard Time and as we consistently
have more participants than we can host
during that time period because there's
only going to be three to five of us on
camera at the time we will open up more
and more time slots and eventually we're
gonna get to have a 24 hour a day 7 day
a week conversation around a question a
week where there gets if you have many
participants you do not I'm indeed mouth
before I started I'm not doing that math
down so where where is this conversation
taking place here on this channel on
YouTube on if for some reason this gets
somewhere else it doesn't link back idea
cafe and we will will be linking to
everybody else's social media if you
come and participate on this channel we
will be linking back to your channel
whether it's on YouTube or Facebook or
periscope or Instagram wherever you want
us to connect people to you or not just
all that is what we will do
why why are we doing the idea cafe
because conversations are powerful they
are a powerful tool to connect us and to
understand one another and we're going
to showcase that and we're going to
brainstorm and work out together what
the best way is for Humanity did have a
conversation by having small intimate
conversations and having conversations
about the larger conversation that's
taking place between all of those time
blocks over the 24/7 once we get to that
point so how can you get involved if you
want to be on camera for next week you
can comment on this week's video I
already have the the participants for
this week you can submit a question that
you would like us to discuss even if you
don't want to discuss it yourselves
and as people upload them that'll be the
clue as to which ones are most powerful
and when there's people who comment on
that not just yes I wanted to hear other
people discuss that but I want to
discuss that that is how you get
involved comment on people's comments
that you want to get involved and you
can email me I just created a new email
address for this project specifically
idea cafe 2020 at gmail.com again his
idea Cafe 2020 at gmail.com I will see
you on Wednesday at 11 a.m. Pacific
Standard Time where we kick off the
conversation that is the idea cafe and
you all get to watch it grow from zero
subscribers to a platform of our very
own to host a conversation that invites
humanity to solve its own problems I'm
so excited
please like and subscribe and hit that
little bell and I will see you on
Wednesday